Would you reach out your hand to save a drowning man
if you thought he might pull you in?
Masked and Anonymous is a drama, music film directed by Larry Charles.
A nation wracked with civil war and social unrest anticipates a giant charity concert, organized by
deceptive promoter Uncle Sweetheart, who plans on raking in huge sums for himself from the event.
Headlining is legendary musician Jack Fate, whose prison
time is cut short with Sweetheart's help.
Meanwhile, journalist Tom Friend investigates the corrupt concert
and sets out to unmask the truth to the public.
Jack Fate, played by Bob Dylan.
Tom Friend, played by Jeff Bridges.
Pagan Lace, played by Penélope Cruz.
Uncle Sweetheart, played by John Goodman.
Nina Veronica, played by Jessica Lange.
Bobby Cupid, played by Luke Wilson.
Masked and Anonymous is a 2003 drama film directed by Larry Charles.
The film was written by Larry Charles (as Sergei
Petrov) and Bob Dylan (as Rene Fontaine).
It stars Dylan alongside a star-heavy cast, including John Goodman, Jeff Bridges, Penélope Cruz, Val Kilmer, Mickey Rourke, Jessica Lange, Luke Wilson, Angela
Bassett, Bruce Dern, Cheech Marin, Ed Harris, Chris Penn, Steven Bauer, Giovanni Ribisi, Michael Paul Chan, Christian Slater, and Fred Ward.
The film explores themes of journalist, concert, rock star, musical.
The tone is emotional.